export const pages = [
    { id: 1, kind: "python", question: "Python問題1", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "A" },
    { id: 2, kind: "python", question: "Python問題2", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "B" },
    { id: 3, kind: "python", question: "Python問題3", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "C" },
    { id: 4, kind: "python", question: "Python問題4", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "D" },
    { id: 5, kind: "python", question: "Python問題5", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "A" },
    { id: 6, kind: "python", question: "Python問題6", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "B" },

    { id: 7, kind: "VBA", question: "VBA問題1", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "A" },
    { id: 8, kind: "VBA", question: "VBA問題2", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "B" },
    { id: 9, kind: "VBA", question: "VBA問題3", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "C" },
    { id: 10, kind: "VBA", question: "VBA問題4", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "D" },
    { id: 11, kind: "VBA", question: "VBA問題5", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "A" },
    { id: 12, kind: "VBA", question: "VBA問題6", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "B" },

    { id: 13, kind: "LPIC", question: "LPIC問題1", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "A" },
    { id: 14, kind: "LPIC", question: "LPIC問題2", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "B" },
    { id: 15, kind: "LPIC", question: "LPIC問題3", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "C" },
    { id: 16, kind: "LPIC", question: "LPIC問題4", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "D" },
    { id: 17, kind: "LPIC", question: "LPIC問題5", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "A" },
    { id: 18, kind: "LPIC", question: "LPIC問題6", select: ["A", "B", "C", "D"], answer: "B" }
  ];
